You clearly pull in the stomach muscles and it relaxes your whole body.
What we want to remember is when when we bring our finger tips up to our shoulders.
We are lightly pressing them down, our hands can go back to our side with our shoulders slightly coming backward.
This is very important that you attain perfect posture.
Also what really helps your chest is to pull in your stomach muscles so that then your entire body relaxes and you can just relax as you attain perfect posture.
As you can clearly see now I have pressed my shoulders down slightly back and my stomach muscles are in and then a front view of perfect posture.
You know attaining perfect posture requires practice and it really helps if you have a mirror. So you can look in the mirror and see yourself.
At a profile and notice if your shoulders are slumped.
Then you're having bad posture.
You can notice in the mirror by pulling the shoulders up.